module.exports = {
  ROUND1QUESTION: [
    {question: 'What is the capital of England? Is it, A, London. B, Edinburgh. C, Cardiff?', answer: 'a'},
    {question: 'Where is Snowdonia located? Is it in, A, West England. B, North England. C, Wales', answer: 'c'},
    {question: 'When did Ireland split into two countries? Was it in, A, 1959. B, 1922. C, 1921', answer: 'b'},
    {question: 'How many countries make up the EU? Are there, A, 28. B, 15. C, 54', answer: 'a'},  
    {question: 'What followed the Bronze Age? Was it, A, The Silver Age. B, The Stone Age. C, The Iron Age', answer: 'c'},
    {question: 'On average, girls leave school with better qualifications than boys? Answer, A, for True, or B, for False', answer: 'a'},
    {question: 'The Channel Islands are self-governing? Answer, A, for True, or B, for False', answer: 'a'},
    {question: 'Which month does St David’s day fall in? Is it in, A, July. B, November. C, March', answer: 'c'},
    {question: 'Roast beef is a traditional food of which country? Is it, A, England. B, Wales. C, Northern Ireland', answer: 'a'},
    {question: 'Where does the Fringe take place? Is it in, A.Liverpool, B.Newcastle, C.Edinburgh', answer: 'c'}
    ],
  ROUND2QUESTION: [
    {question: 'Where did the people of the Bronze Age bury their dead? Was it in A,Graveyards. B,Round Barrows. C,Coffin House', answer: 'b'},
    {question: 'Hadrian’s Wall is a popular UNESCO World Heritage Site? Answer, A, for True, or B, for False', answer: 'a'},
    {question: 'Where in Scotland is known as the home of golf? Is it A, St Andrews. B, Glasgow. C, Edinburgh', answer: 'a'},
    {question: 'Who mapped the coast of Australia? Was it, A, James Cook. B, Admiral Nelson. C, Francis Drake', answer: 'a'},
    {question: 'How old is Big Ben? Is it A, one hundred and fifty years old. B, one hundred years old. C, two hundred years old', answer: 'a'},
    {question: 'Who was the prime minister during World War Two? Was it A, Margeret Thatcher. B, Winston Churchill. C, Tony Blair', answer: 'b'},
    {question: 'Who is Queen Elizabeth the second married to? Is it, A, Prince Harry. B, Prince Charles. C, Prince Philip', answer: 'c'},
    {question: 'Who was Henry Purcell? Was he A, An Artist. B, A Musician. C, A Scientist', answer: 'a'},
    {question: 'Northern Ireland has its own banknotes which are valid everywhere in the UK. Answer, A, for True, or B, for False' , answer: 'a'},
    {question: 'How long did the Romans stay in Britain? Was it A, Four Hundred Years. B, Six Hundred Years. C, Three Hundred Years', answer: 'a'}
    ]
  }